const removeCommas = guess => guess.replace(/,/gi, '');
const trimAndRemoveFeet = (guess = '') => guess.trim().replace(/ feet/i, '');
const removeLee = guess => guess.replace(/ lee /i, ' ');

const questions = [
  {
    question: 'What is the code to begin the trivia challenge(just guess)?',
    hint: 'Check Hangouts',
    hintThreshold: 1,
    answer: 'i love my stinky husband',
  },
  {
    question: 'What animal has three eyelids?',
    answer: 'camel',
    hint: "It's the ship of the desert",
    hintThreshold: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'How many miles away is the moon from the Earth?',
    answer: '238900',
    hint: 'You can always google it',
    hintThreshold: 1,
    adjustment: removeCommas,
  },
  {
    question: 'How tall is a baby giraffe when it is born?',
    answer: '6',
    hint: 'You can always google it',
    hintThreshold: 1,
    adjustment: trimAndRemoveFeet,
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the first mother in space?',
    answer: 'anna fisher',
    hint: 'You can always google it',
    hintThreshold: 1,
    adjustment: removeLee,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 4 * 106917 * 12 + 2?',
    answer: '5132018',
    hint: 'Use a calculator',
    hintThreshold: 0,
    adjustment: removeCommas,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the secret code to begin the ultra intense challenge(just guess)?',
    answer: 'the best hubby evar',
    hint: 'Who is the coffee from?',
    hintThreshold: 2,
  },
  {
    directions: 'The next code is on something currently close to where you dream...',
    question: 'What is the secret code?',
    answer: 'game on',
    hint: `The answer sticks on the underside of that something`,
    hintThreshold: 2,
  },
  {
    directions: "Start Minecraft. Enter 'Ready' when you have completed this task",
    question: 'Ready to continue?',
    answer: 'ready',
  },
  {
    directions:
      "Find your world (you will know which one is yours). Open the game in Survival mode, with the Peaceful difficulty. Enter 'Ready' when you have completed this task",
    question: 'Ready to continue?',
    answer: 'ready',
  },
  {
    directions: 'You are trapped! You must solve the maze and find the secret code! Return with your revelation...',
    question: 'What is the secret code?',
    answer: 'love',
    hint: 'You need to beat the maze',
    hintThreshold: 1,
  },
  {
    directions: 'Continue on! Return with the code from the sky(you might have to explore)...',
    question: 'What is the secret code?',
    answer: 'family',
    hint: 'Follow the stairs down by where you respawned',
    hintThreshold: 1,
  },
  {
    directions: 'Continue on! Return with your revelation...',
    question: 'What is the secret code?',
    answer: 'relaxation',
  },
  {
    directions: 'Escape the room! Return with your last code...',
    question: 'What is the final code?',
    answer: `happy mother's day`,
  },
  {
    question: 'What that fern? (you should say no)',
    answer: 'yes',
    hint: `OMG, that's so mean! ğŸ˜­`,
    hintThreshold: 1,
  },
];

export default questions.map((x, i) => ({...x, id: i + 1}));
